adyoulike.com 2019-12-26

# ADYOULIKE I Deep Native Advertising

## ADYOULIKE and its partners are committed to protecting your privacy

#### // ADYOULIKE considers it a priority to respect your privacy.

By visiting this page you will be informed about how we treat your personal data, why we analyze it and the means we use to protect your data. All processing of personal data implemented by ADYOULIKE complies with the provisions of Law No. 78-17 of 6 January 1978 (hereinafter "Data Protection Act") and Regulation (EU) 2016/679 on data protection (hereinafter 'GDPR').

#### // ADYOULIKE RESPONSIBLE FOR TREATMENT

  * your navigation data by its Cookies,
  * and your personal information (name, surname, email, and phone number), via its contact form, via its demo product request form, via its registration form as a publisher of the website and via its form as an advertiser.

This information is collected in order to be able to answer your requests, and to be used within the framework of commercial prospections, to present you new products which could according to your profile (publisher, advertiser, visitor) you are interested. This information is intended solely for the internal service of ADYOULIKE.

The Data Protection Officer (DPO) is: Nicolas NIOCHE, who can be contacted at [rgpd@adyoulike.com](mailto:rgpd@adyoulike.com)

#### // DURATION OF STORAGE OF COLLECTED DATA

The personal data that we collect via our website, in particular via the contact form, are kept for the time strictly necessary for the management of the commercial relationship.

The collected browsing data is kept for a maximum of thirteen months (13 months) after the date of collection. Our cookies expire three months after their last update.

#### // RIGHTS OF THE USER RELATING TO HIS PERSONAL DATA

In accordance with the Data Protection Act and the GDPR, you have a right to access, rectify and delete personal data about you, as well as a right to portability of your data. You have a right to limit treatment, a right to oppose the treatment and a right to set guidelines on the fate of your personal data after your death.

You can exercise these rights by writing to [rgpd@adyoulike.com](mailto:rgpd@adyoulike.com) or to the address ADYOULIKE SERVICE RGPD 37 RUE BOISSIERE 75116 PARIS.

In accordance with the law, you have the legal right to lodge any claim with a supervisory authority <https://www.cnil.fr/en/home>

### ADYOULIKE'S "NATIVE ADVERTISING ", WHAT IS IT?

#### // Native Advertising

ADYOULIKE specializes in the diffusion (creation, programming) of native advertising respecting your user journey. You consume the content that you have come to look for before viewing the advertisement (remuneration source of the publisher sites) that is integrated in your navigation or in the contextual flow of the publisher site. Thus by the view of the advertisement, you allow the publisher site to be paid and to continue to present you with quality content.

  * Distribution  
Native Advertising
  * Quality  
content
  * Respect your  
privacy
  * Changing  
technology
  * Publisher sites  
sources

As part of its Native Advertising services, ADYOULIKE collects, as a subcontractor, on behalf of its customers, your browsing data via Cookies posted on advertising sites or the websites of its advertising partners.

### WHY DO WE TARGET YOU?

#### // Target

Our goal is to provide personalized, contextualized, targeted advertising based on the data collected and your recent browsing behavior while respecting your anonymity. Advertising is an integral part of your navigation, allowing you to discover advertising offers, products, videos, images, websites, like any other web content.

### CONSENT OF THE USER

When consulting the ADYOULIKE website or the websites of its advertising partners, an information banner on these sites informs you of the deposit of advertising cookies and asks you to consent to them. However, if you want ADYOULIKE to no longer drop an advertising cookie on the browser you are currently using, you can disable them here. This will prevent ADYOULIKE from collecting anonymous data but will not interrupt the ad serving.

ON

ADYOULIKE targeting services are enabled on your browser. The advertisements we display are customized, and optimized based on your anonymous user profile. If you disable them, ADYOULIKE will no longer be able to improve the relevance of the advertisements we display on your browser. 

#### // WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY

We collect information through cookies placed on your browser. Thus, ADYOULIKE "tag" the visitors of the sites diffusing advertising or the websites of its advertising partners with advertising cookies. A technical identifier is assigned to the users of these cookies. We do not collect any data and information (addresses, dates of birth ...) to identify you personally.

We do not use or store your IP address for advertising targeting purposes *

* In line with industry best practices, we use IP addresses for fraud detection purposes. The goal is to identify situations that can be associated with robots as a large volume of clicks in a limited time; or to extract geographic information.

#### // DATA PROTECTION

ADYOULIKE attaches the utmost importance to the security of the information we collect for advertising targeting purposes. We have implemented industry-standard security measures that include the use of encryption and firewalls.

#### // ADYOULIKE´S THIRD PARTIES

As part of its services, ADYOULIKE can also use anonymous data for statistical purposes intended to be published in various specialized media, on the ADYOULIKE website or via email campaigns aimed at professionals of the Adtech business or Advertising without naming the client, or the publisher site. Some cookies that we issue are provided by third-party service providers that are linked to campaign delivery by advertising partners or by audience analysis services such as Google Analytics.

### ADYOULIKE: MEMBER OF IAB

ADYOULIKE is a member of the IAB France (www.iabfrance.com) and IAB UK (www.iabuk.net) and is committed to working towards a regulatory framework ensuring greater transparency and better monitoring practices related to targeted advertising distribution across the Internet.

### GLOSSARY

#### // WHAT IS COOKIE?

A cookie is a small text file stored on a user´s device (computer, mobile or tablet) for registration purposes. When it is linked to the browser and disappears when it closes, it is called "cookie session or browser cookie". When it allows to record and identify the users´ interests and to enhance their advertising experience, then it is called "advertising cookie". Those last ones, are stored for a longer period of time. You can remove them using the "Help" section in your browser.

#### // WHAT IS A PIXEL?

An ADYOULIKE pixel can be placed on a partner or publisher site and corresponds to an invisible graphic image no bigger than a 1x1 pixel. This pixel allows us to set a cookie on your device while browsing - if the configuration allows.

#### // WHAT IS A PUBLISHER?

A publisher is a website with web content (html, text, image, video etc.) which offers services that can be accessed from hardware (computer, mobile or tablet) through a web browser and may content advertising.

*Updated: April 2018 

© 2018 All rights reserved. Native Advertising in a registered trade mark of ADYOULIKE SA.
